Preliminary Guide to the Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services records, 1821 ca.-2005 RG0006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services records
circa 1821-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services
RG0006
14.25 Linear Feet
Materials in this collection include publications, committee files, ledgers, pamphlets, and posters. They range in date from circa 1821 to 2005.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials were transferred to the University Archives by the Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services of The George Washington University reports to the President. The office oversees a wide range of areas related to student life: Admissions (undergraduate), Athletics and Recreation, Financial Assistance, Dean of Students, Career Center, Community Living and Learning Center, University Counseling Center, International Services, Marvin Center, Mount Vernon Campus Life Office, Multicultural Student Services Center, Office of Community Service, Parent Services, Presidential Administrative Fellowship, Recreational Sports and Fitness Services, SASS Communication and Technology, Student Activities Center, Student Health Services, Summer Camp: The GW Summer Tour, Student Judicial Service, Colonial Inauguration, Disability Support Service, Center for Alcohol and other Drug Education, and University Police.
In 2003 the name was changed to Senior Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services. Before 1989 it was named Vice President for Student Affairs.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include publications, committee files, ledgers, pamphlets, and posters. They range in date from circa 1821 to 2005, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services.
Collection Organization
Organized into ten series: Records, Office files, Office files, Student Club Cooperative Store [Student Union], Scrapbook, Communication, Communication, University counseling center, Communication and Creative Services, and Student Activities Center.
Washington (D.C.); Scrapbooks; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Counseling; Athletics; Recreation; Students; Students, Foreign; George Washington University. Mount Vernon Campus; George Washington University. Cloyd Heck Marvin Center
- Records, circa 1821-2005; RG0006 Series 1; 2 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains programs, flyers, brochures, maps, correspondence, invitations, schedules, reports, memorandums, handbooks, guides, minutes, applications, publications, a survey, newsletters, rosters, and calendars. They range in date from approximately 1821 to 2005. The materials concern student orientation, information for parents, recreational activities, Recreational Sports and Fitness services, job descriptions, the Five-to-One Program, residence assistants, handicapped awareness programs, regulatory procedures for student life, campus unity, student regulations, student's rights, student responsibilities, honor constitutions, "Inertia", career conferences, financial aid, activities books, Parent's Day, Family Week, Parent's Week, May Day activities, "The GWU Money Manual", student life, open houses, the Student Activities Center, leisure guides, student activities on campus, blood drives, skills for living series, policies and procedures for student activities, Welcome Week, orientation, the Presidential Administrative Fellows Program, "The Campus Calendar", "This Month in Washington D.C.", "This Week at GWU", annual report of the Student Activities Office, student organizations, the Student Council, Student Health Services, transfer students, information for freshmen, event calendars, academic calendars, alumni calendars, GW administrative responses to student protests, the Maury Hall takeover, "The Cox Commission Report and George Washington University", anti-war strikes, the Office of Safety and Security, identification cards, Colonial Express Shuttle Bus, 4-Ride Escort Service, the University Police Department, "Security Blanket", campus security, study abroad, "GW Abroad", the International Student Society, international student advising, "Greek Wire", rosters of student organizations, the Office of Greek Affairs, Colonial Inauguration (student orientation), and faculty advisors.
  The information includes materials and publications produced from the Student Activities Office; the International Services Office; Office of Public Relations; Office of Parent Services; The George Washington University Parents' Association; the Office of the Dean of Students; the University Activities Office; the Office of Campus Life; the Student Affairs Office; Disabled Student Services; the Office of Student and Academic Support Services Communication and Technology; the Student Placement Office; the Student Financial Aid Office; the Dean of Summer Sessions; the Office of Greek Affairs, and the Student Activities and Organizations Office.
  Additionally, a book of the minutes of the Student Council for the Class of 1921 officers is included.
  Formerly vertical files.
  - Student and Academic Support Services, Office of, 1988-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Student and Alumni Career Services, Office of, 02/25/1953-08/1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Student Financial Aid Office, circa 1960-01/25/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student Financial Aid Office Brochures, 1962-1973, 02/1962-08/1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Financial Aid Office Brochures, 1974-1988, 1973-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student Health Service, 02/24/1970-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Student Life, 1949-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Student Life Class of 1921 - Minute book (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Student Protests, 1960-1969, 05/09/1969-06/22/1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Student Protests, 1970-1982, 05/06/1970-04/22/1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Student Protests Maury Hall takeover, April 1969, 04/24/1969-07/1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Student Protests Student Anti-War Strike, 1936-1937, 04/10/1935-04/22/1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Students--Freshmen, 09/23/1925-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Students Transfer Students, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - University Calendar, 08/29/1952-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - University Calendar, 1909, 1940, 10/11/1909-1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - University Calendar, 1961-1968, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - University Calendar, 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations Registers of Student Organizations (1967- ), 1967-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1995-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Advisors--Handbooks, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - International Services Office, 08/1980-10/1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - International Services Office Study Abroad, 1999-2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - International Students, 11/11/1949-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - International Students--Activities, 04/05/1957-04/1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - International Student Advising, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Greek Affairs, Office of, 04/02/1999-04/2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Orientations, 09/18/1939-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Parents Day, 05/05/1944-10/13/1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Parents/Family Weekend, 03/11/1966-10/15/2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Parents Information, 08/1970-10/15/1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Safety And Security, Office Of /University Police, 12/02/1970-2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes organizational history of the Office of Public Safety and Emergency Management, timeline from 2001 to 2008, list of IAEM awards, OPSEM images/logos, and staff roster.
  - Safety And Security, Office Of / University Police Colonial Express and Escort Service, 10/1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Safety And Security, Office Of / University Police Safety Handbook, 1973, 06/1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Student Activities Activities books, 1934, 1947, 1954, 1934-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Student Activities May Day activities, 1954-1966, 05/07/1954-05/06/1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Student Activities Recreational Activities, 06/1941-2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office, 04/06/1970-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Announcements, 1965-03/17/1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Manuals, 1948, 1952, 1965, 1985, 1948-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Orientation information, 1953-2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Presidential Administrative Fellows Program, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Publications - Campus Calendar, 1972-1981, 1972-1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Publications This Month in Washington, 1972-1982, 06/1972-12/1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Publications This Week at GWU, 1971-1973, 09/06/1971-01/06/1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Publications This Week at GWU, 1974-1976, 01/07/1974-02/29/1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Report, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Student Activities Information, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Student Activities and Organizations Office Student Organizations, 1966-04/16/1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Student Affairs Office, 05/08/1968-1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Student Affairs Office - Disabled Student Services, 10/1980-10/23/1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Student Affairs Office Regulatory Procedures for Student Life, c.1970, 09/09/1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Student Affairs Office Report on Campus Unity, 1989, 01/01/1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Student Affairs Office Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1970-1989, 08/07/1970-1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Student Affairs Office Student Rights and Responsibilities, 1990-2004, 1990-07/2004 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Student Affairs Office Student Rights and Responsibilities History, 1821-1969, circa 1821-03/25/1971 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Office files, 1941-1987; RG0006 Series 2; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series contains assorted GW publications (including cherry trees and student handbooks) and smith scrapbook materials. The material dates from 1941-87.
  Formerly ACC#20
  This series is unprocessed, please ask staff for assistance.
- Office files, 1969-1990; RG0006 Series 3; 3 Linear feet
  This series contains information about the Carnegie Commission on Higher Education sponsored research studies, and student affairs committee files. These records date from 1969-90.
  Formerly ACC #188
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.
- Student Club Cooperative Store [Student Union], 1940-1964; RG0006 Series 4; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 1)
  This series contains three ledgers of the student club cooperative store (vol. 1 [1940-1946]; vol.2 [1946-1952]; vol.3 [1952-1964])
  Formerly ACC#266
- Scrapbook, RG0006 Series 5; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains a scrapbooks on student unrest in the 1960's, both GW and nationwide [see also call number ld 1936.G46 1969 in special collections about Maury Hall takeover hearings].
  Formerly ACC#330
- Communication, 1989-1996; RG0006 Series 6; 2 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains publications, admissions applications, and files related to subjects such as Colonials Basketball, Colonial Inauguration, connections, counseling center, international students, multicultural student services center, planner and student handbook, residential life, transfer brochure, UPD pride, and welcome week. These records date from 1989-96.
  Formerly ACC #482
  - Alumni Admissions Program Manual, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Admissions Program, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Admissions Program Invite, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Admissions Program, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Application for Admission or Readmission to Undergraduate Degree Status, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Application for Undergraduate Admissions, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Application for Undergraduate Admissions, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Application for Undergraduate Admissions, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Basketball: Clinton Postcard, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Basketball: "Colonials", 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Basketball: "Colonials", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Big To Do", 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Career Center, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Career Center, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - College Program Brochure - Recruitment, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - College Program Brochure, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - College Program Brochure Card, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - College Program Brochure Card, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Colonnade Gallery, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Colonnade Gallery, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Colonial Challenge, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Colonial Challenge, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Colonial Challenge, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Colonial Challenge, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Colonial Inauguration: Congressional Roll Call, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Colonial Inauguration, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Colonial inauguration, 1990-2013; Series 6 Box 3 (Box 3)
  - "Connections" Poster and Reply, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Connections" Poster, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Connections" Newsletter, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    General note
    Spring, Summer, and Fall
  - "Connections" Newsletter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Spring and Fall
  - "Connections" Video Survey, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Counseling Center, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Counseling Center, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Counselor Breakfast Invitation, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - D.C. Metro Day, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Disabled Student Services, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Educational Opportunity Program Day, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Educational Opportunity Program Day, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Fall Receptions - Admissions, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Fall Receptions - Admissions, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Financial Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Financial Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Financial Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Financial Aid "Little Book of Big Answers", 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Financial Aid "Good Card", 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Rush, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Fall
  - Fresh Facts, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - George's Birthday Card Yield Piece, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Get Going! College Program Brochure, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Honors Application, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Honors Program Brochure and Application, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Honors Program Brochure, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Hungry for Music, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - International Services Office, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - International Student Viewbook and Application, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - International Services Pre-Arrival Guide, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - International Services Pre-Arrival Guide, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - International Services Pre-Arrival Guide, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Interview Card, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Invitation to Visit, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Invitation to Visit, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Medical School Brochure, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Medical School Brochure, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Medical School Brochure, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Multicultural Student Service Center, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Multicultural Student Weekend, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Multicultural Students Day, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Multicultural Students Day, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Offers of Admission, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - 175th Gold Seal, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Open House, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Open House/Colonial Convention, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Open House, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Open House, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Parents' Day, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Parents' Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Parents' Handbook, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Planner and Student Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Planner and Student Handbook, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Planner and Student Handbook, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Planner Media Guide, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Planner and Student Handbook, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Planner and Student Handbook, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Arts Scholarship, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Presidential Arts Scholarship, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Arts Scholarship, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Presidential Honors Scholarship Awards Program, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Presidential Science Scholar Award Program, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Reminder to Apply Card Part I, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reminder to Apply Card Part II, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Residential Life: "Living and Learning Residential Programs", 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Residential Life, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Residential Life, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - School of Business and Public Management Brochure, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Brochure, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Brochure, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences Brochure IRB, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Search, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Search "Hey!", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Search "20052", 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Search, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Search "Solid Facts", 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Sexual Assault Guide, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Spring Visit, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Spring Visit, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Summer Scholar Program, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Transfer Brochure, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Transfer Brochure, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 21st Century Scholars, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 21st Century Scholars, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - University Police Department "Pride" Brochure, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - University Police Department "Pride" Brochure, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - University Police Department "Pride" Brochure, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - University Police Department "Security Blanket", 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Viewbook, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Viewbook "Connections" Software, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Viewbook "Connections", 1990 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Viewbook "20052", 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Viewbook "Something Happens Here", 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Viewbook "Something Happens Here", 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Visit Brochure, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Visit Brochure, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Welcome Week, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Welcome Week "Fresh Experience", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Fine Art of Campus Life Poster, 1996-1997; RG0006 Series 7; 1 Linear foot (Map-folder 1)
  This series contains a Fine art of campus life poster and planner for the year 1996-97.
  Formerly ACC#609
- University counseling center, 1999-2000; RG0006 Series 8; 0.25 Linear feet (Map-folder 1)
  This series contains five posters dealing with 20th annual chalk-in and counseling services, for the year 1999-2000.
  Formerly ACC#811
- Communication and Creative Services, circa 1983-2000; RG0006 Series 9; no content (Box 5, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 2, Box 1, Box 4, Box 3)
  This series consists of photographs, negatives, slides, and videotapes of campus scenes. The materials range in date from 1983-2000 and were transferred to University Archives in 2006.
  Box 1-7 temporarily housed in 704S.
  - Connections Video Tour 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GWU Security Video-Your Community Your Choice, 05/18/1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Connections Video Tour 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Hillary Rodham Clinton At George Washington University, 05/08/1995-05/09/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Real Movie Tour 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GWU Colonials Inauguration, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Real Movie Tour 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - GWU Sample Tape With Additional Footage, 07/11/1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Excerpts from Croak or The Last Frog, 08/1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GW Colonials-1. "The Play" 2. "Fantastic Finishes", 03/03/1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - G.W.U Colonial Inauguration-1. The University and it's City 2. Things You'll Learn 3. Guide to Student Life, 06/09/1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GW Campus Planner Focus Group, 04/18/1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Something Happens Here The Movie, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Promo video for GW, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    No narration, only music
  - The George Washington University Connections 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GW Promo video "Start to Finish", circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rodney Johnson Presentation Colonial Inauguration, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - GWU TV Commercials, Recruitment Film, 01/10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Newschannel 8-George Washington Spotlight (Chris Changery), circa 03/20/1990-circa 03/21/1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Aired 3/20 and 3/21
  - George Washington University '95 CI Video-1. It's Your Four Years 2. Oh, The Things You'll Learn 3. Quick Guide to Student Life, 06/08/1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Neighborhood Video, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Something Happens Here The Movie, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - George Washington University Basketball Video Yearbook, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The 2000-2001 George Washington University Basketball Highlights Video (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Toward The 21st Century The George Washington University-Arrival of Pres. Trachtenberg, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - VWBK-Cathy Pickar, Quintin Garalt, Jim Peterson, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Audiocassette
  - VWBK-A. Ambassador Palmer and Dr. Epstein B. Epstein and Tina Holmes, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Side 1: Helin-col. cao, Dean East-fac Side 2: Dean East, Susan Stromin-USHP, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Black Tie Optional-The 1989 George Washington University TROUBADOURS (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Slides in binder: University Tour, VIVA, OCL Kick-Off, Parents' Day, President's Anniversary, Presidential Inauguration, Salsa Dance, Scholarship Nite, Senior Week
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Binder of slides: Homecoming, International Week, Information Center/Hot Dog Stand, Marvin Center, Marvin Gras
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Binder of slides: Four shot studying, Five shot Mt. Vernon, Three shot Mt. Vernon studying, Lacrosse, Basketball, Rose Garden classroom, Sports
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Binder of slides: Faculty and staff, Sports, GW Events Fun Day/Others, GW Events White House State Visit, AAPC Conference, License Party, License Plate, Spring Visit, Parents' Day
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)